Sometimes it's hard to find your way.
Down in the Valley is a drama, romance, thriller
film directed by David Jacobson.
On a trip to the beach, a teenage girl named Tobe meets a charismatic stranger named
Harlan, who dresses like a cowboy and claims to be a former ranch hand.
The pair feel an instant attraction and begin a relationship, but
her father, a lawman, is suspicious of her lover.
Harlan, played by Edward Norton.
Tobe, played by Evan Rachel Wood.
Wade, played by David Morse.
Lonnie, played by Rory Culkin.
Charlie, played by Bruce Dern.
Steve, played by John Diehl.
Down in the Valley is a 2005 American neo-western drama film starring
Edward Norton, Evan Rachel Wood, David Morse and Rory Culkin.
The film made its debut in the Un Certain Regard section at the 2005 Cannes Film Festival on
May 13, and made its limited theatrical release in North America on May 5, 2006.
The film explores themes of beach, indian territory,
stetson, san fernando valley, strange person.
The tone is emotional and intense.